<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Etc on Jiman Hwang</title>
    <link>/etc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Etc on Jiman Hwang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/etc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Dean&#39;s list 2015 Spring</title>
      <link>/etc/deans-list-2015-spring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/etc/deans-list-2015-spring/</guid>
      <description>Thanks. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reversing Lecture(undergraduate)</title>
      <link>/etc/reversing-lectureundergraduate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/etc/reversing-lectureundergraduate/</guid>
      <description>A reversing lecture was held June 5, 2015. by HIT lab for undergraduate students who were participating dissertation project, and some of students in software department. The course materials were [Easy Keygen], and [ImagePrc] at reversing.kr. Thank you for your attendance even upcoming final exam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SKKU bug bounty</title>
      <link>/etc/skku-bug-bounty/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/etc/skku-bug-bounty/</guid>
      <description>SKKU bug bounty(2015. 5.4. – 5.15.) was the first bug bounty held among universities in Korea. Though there was a limitation about target sites, it was not bad considering the fact that it was the first try.
I found one that steals name, site ID, department, student ID, cellphone #, address, and email of members of Sungkyunkwan univ. including professors, and staffs as well as students regardless of graduation. I wish they break the limitation, not just some sites, i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduation project(undergraduate, Computer Science)</title>
      <link>/etc/graduation-projectundergraduate-computer-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/etc/graduation-projectundergraduate-computer-science/</guid>
      <description>Analysis and Implementation of Remote Code Execution through Flash Player Vulnerability and Crafted Web Site
Implementation of CVE-2014-0515. Not bad that I explored some innerwork of Flash player.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a brief procedure about how my work operates.
 The attacker runs a web server and builds a site that uses the malicious flash player file. A victim connects to the site. Note that anyone can be a victim if he/she connects to the site without patched Flash Player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Reverse Lecture</title>
      <link>/etc/open-reverse-lecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/etc/open-reverse-lecture/</guid>
      <description>An open lecture was held by HIT lab regarding basic reversing skills for undergraduate students. Students who were interesting in reversing participated in the lecture.
Poster
Four classes for two days(2015. 4.7 / 4.9), I lectured the last one. I recomposed this exploit which includes stack overflow, how to build a PoC, and what payload could be.
Lecture material: GOM.pdf</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduation project(undergraduate, Mechanical Engineering)</title>
      <link>/etc/graduation-projectundergraduate-mechanical-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/etc/graduation-projectundergraduate-mechanical-engineering/</guid>
      <description>As a senior in Mechanical Engineering, I was demanded to participate in a project for my diploma. Among many projects, one in RISE lab intrigued me. The project entailed programming skills as well as knowledge of mechanical engineering.
Problem:
 Given a range sensor, make a mobile robot navigate a corridor environment. Full exploration is proven by acquiring the entire map.
 Generalized Voronoi Graph(GVG) is one of famous methods for a mobile robot to walk through corridor areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robot competition</title>
      <link>/etc/robot-competition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/etc/robot-competition/</guid>
      <description>Check out this video for information about Robot competition, powered by RISE lab.
It was during the class named Design Laboratory on Vibration and Dynamic Systems on the Spring, 2014.
Here is our team&amp;rsquo;s product.
        Given some elements; three motors, two laser sensors, one sonar sensor, and peripheral parts, it was hard for us to defeat each stage in 3 minutes, especially the challenges including collecting blocks, and climbing up a slope.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ConnApp 2013 - Inaudible frequency communication</title>
      <link>/etc/connapp-2013-inaudible-frequency-communication/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/etc/connapp-2013-inaudible-frequency-communication/</guid>
      <description>ConnApp is a mobile app competition, one of subprojects of Seoul Accord. Our team(Kiyeol Lim, Jiman Hwang, Dongeui Kim) made two simple apps(a provider and a beneficiary) that communicates each other over inaudible frequency.
In a market, each section has one or more providing speaker, making an inaudible sound. On the other hand, a shopper&amp;rsquo;s smartphone operating the beneficiary app receives and analyzes the sound, and shows a web page provided by seller.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
